uniprogy.com 2010-03-12

# UniProgy - Reader Site

## Privacy Policy

Effective: December 1, 2009

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the UniProgy website. On some pages, you can answer survey questions and register in order to save your vote. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Gender
  * Age
  * Location
  * Email address

On pages where you can invite your friends to leave their vote on our site, you can submit information about other people. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

  * Email Address

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information we collect on our survey to support better decision-making in our company. We do not accept advertising on our web sites and will absolutely not use your email addresses for any purpose not connected with the management of our services. We use a type of cookie, called a session object, to maintain the connection between pages during the time that you are entering responses to the survey or while you're logged in to your account. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by a secure login into the members area. If for some reason you cannot login or have lost your password you can use the "lost password" tool. If that process has failed you may then contact us and to protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. There is a security limit of 1 request per 7 days to protect your privacy.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [support@uniprogy.com](mailto:support@uniprogy.com).
